BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.1275: Weyerhaeuser Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1967-1973 (Box 5, Folder 1275)
  - Code no.2500: Acme Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 2500)
  - Code no.2502: Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2502)
  - Code no.2507: Atlantic Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1956-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2507)
  - Code no.2508: Babcock and Wilcox Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 1082, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2508)
  - Code no.2509: Standard Steel and United Steelworkers of America Local 1940, 1959-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2509)
  - Code no.2512: Colorado Fuel and Iron Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2512)
  - Code no.2513: John A. Roebling's Sons Division and United Steelworkers of America Local 2110, 1960-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2513)
  - Code no.2518: Detroit Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 2518)
  - Code no.2523: Great Lakes Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2523)
  - Code no.2524: Inland Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2524)
  - Code no.2591: Aluminum Company of America and Aluminum Workers International Union Locals 110, 405, 105, 100, 115, 415, 445, 104, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2591)
  - Code no.2599: Chase Brass and Copper Co. and Chase Brass and Copper Workers Union Local 1565, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2599)
  - Code no.2603: Inco and United Steelworkers of America Local 40, 1960-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2603)
  - Code no.2604: Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2604)
  - Code no.2605: Mueller Brass Co. and UAW Local 44, 1957-1969 (Box 8, Folder 2605)
  - Code no.2611: Reynolds Metals Company and Aluminum Workers International Union Locals 200 and 210, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 2611)
  - Code no.2612: Reynolds Metals Company and Aluminum Workers International Union Locals 155, 400, 425, 160, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 2612)
  - Code no.2613: Western Electric Company, Inc. and Communication Equipment Workers, Inc., 1961-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2613)
  - Code no.2614: National Lead Company and UAW Local s 1056, 1057, 1058, 257, 1962-1968 (Box 8, Folder 2614)
  - Code no.2632: Central Foundry Company of Holt, Alabama and International Molders and Allied Workers Union Locals 63, 67, 1965- 1970 (Box 8, Folder 2632)
  - Code no.2661: Western Electric Company, Inc. and CWA Local 1162, 1960-1963 (Box 8, Folder 2661)
  - Code no.2906: American Hardware Corporation and IAM AFL-CIO, Lodge 1137, 1958-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2906)
  - Code no.2908: Stanley Works and Stanley Tools Division and IAM Local 1433, 1960-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2908)
  - Code no.2909: True Temper Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1966-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2909)
  - Code no.3355: Xerox Data Systems and IAM Lodge 1578, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 3355)
  - Code no.3605: Sangamo Electric Company and Selco Union, 1961-1968 (Box 8, Folder 3605)
  - Code no.3607: George D. Roper Corporation and Metal Trades Department-AFL-CIO, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 3607)
  - Code no.3617: General Electric Company and IUE, 1960-1966 (Box 8, Folder 3617)
  - Code no.3625: Westinghouse Electric Corporation and IBEW, 1960-1966 (Box 8, Folder 3625)
  - Code no.3629: Westinghouse Electric Corporation and Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1960-1966 (Box 8, Folder 3629)
  - Code no.3633: Norge Division and IAM Local 554, 1959-1965 (Box 8, Folder 3633)
  - Code no.3641: Sunbeam Corporation and IAM District 8, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 3641)
  - Code no.3642: Whirlpool Corporation and IAM Local 1918, 1960-1967 (Box 8, Folder 3642)
  - Code no.3643: Arrow-Hart and Hegeman Electric Company and IBEW Local 1013, 1958-1973 (Box 8, Folder 3643)
  - Code no.3660: Radio Corporation of America and IBEW Local 2237, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3660)
  - Code no.3666: Amphenol-Borg Electronics Corporation and IBEW Local 1031, 1960-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3666)
  - Code no.3667: Automatic Electric Company and IAM District 8, 1961-1966 (Box 8, Folder 3667)
  - Code no.3668: Automatic Electric Company and IBEW Local 713, 1961-1970 (Box 9, Folder 3668)
  - Code no.3669: Bendix Radio Division and Industrial Radio Lodge 1561, 1959-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3669)
  - Code no.3675: Philco Corporation and Radio and Television Workers Local 102, 1958-1967 (Box 9, Folder 3675)
  - Code no.3676: Western Electric Company, Inc. and CWA, 1961-1970 (Box 9, Folder 3676)
  - Code no.3677: Teletype Corporation and Teletype Employees' Industrial Union, 1962-1967 (Box 9, Folder 3677)
  - Code no.3678: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1470, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 3678)
  - Code no.3680: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1504, 1960-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3680)
  - Code no.3681: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1942, 1960-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3681)
  - Code no.3682: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1974, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 3682)
  - Code no.3683: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 2021, 1961-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3683)
  - Code no.3684: Western Electric Company, Inc. and CWA, 1960-1970 (Box 10, Folder 3684)
  - Code no.3685: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1806, 1960-1970 (Box 10, Folder 3685)
  - Code no.3686: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1522, 1961-1965 (Box 10, Folder 3686)
  - Code no.3687: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1859, 1960-1970 (Box 10, Folder 3687)
  - Code no.3688: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1898, 1964-1971 (Box 10, Folder 3688)
  - Code no.3689: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 2020, 1963-1971 (Box 10, Folder 3689)
  - Code no.3692: General Instrument Corporation, F.W. Sickles Division and IBEW Local 1500, 1960-1972 (Box 10, Folder 3692)
  - Code no.3693: Hughes Aircraft Company and Electronic and Space Technicians Local 1553, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 3693)
  - Code no.3697: Sangamo Electric Company and IAM Lodge 1986, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 3697)
  - Code no.3698: Sylvania Electric Products Inc. and IUE, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 3698)
  - Code no.3701: Champion Spark Plug Company and UAW Locals 272, 12, 1959-1971 (Box 10, Folder 3701)
  - Code no.3713: Gould-National Batteries, Inc. and IBEW, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 3713)
  - Code no.3722: Leviton Manufacturing Company and IBEW Local 1274, 1962-1971 (Box 11, Folder 3722)
  - Code no.3724: Leviton Manufacturing Company and IBEW Local Union 3, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 3724)
  - Code no.3728: Lear Siegler, Inc. and IAM Local 54, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 3728)
  - Code no.3729: Warwick Electronics Inc. and IUE Local 1022, 1965-1972 (Box 11, Folder 3729)
  - Code no.3730: Sylvania Electric Products Inc. and IUE Local 352, 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3730)
  - Code no.3732: Jefferson Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1031, 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3732)
  - Code no.3735: ITT Cannon Electric and UAW Local 509, 1965-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3735)
  - Code no.3736: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 2188, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3736)
  - Code no.3740: Westinghouse Electric Corporation and IBEW Local 1833, 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 3740)
  - Code no.3742: National Video Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 3742)
  - Code no.3745: Sylvania Electric Products, Inc., Emporium Plants and United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1967- 1970 (Box 11, Folder 3745)
  - Code no.3746: Magnavox Company and IAM Lodge 431, 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 3746)
  - Code no.3750: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1470, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 3750)
  - Code no.3751: Arvin Industries and IAM Local 888, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 3751)
  - Code no. 3753: Standard Components and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 1003, AFL-CIO, 1969- 1972 (Box 11, Folder 3753)
  - Code no.3784: Bendix Corporation, Scintilla Division and IAM Local 1529, 1960-1971 (Box 11, Folder 3784)
  - Code no.3785: Seeburg Corporation and Warehouse and Mail Order Employees Union Local 743, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 3785)
  - Code no.3786: Hoover Company and IBEW Local 1985, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 3786)
  - Code no.4000: Carter Carburetor, Inc. and UAW Local 819, 1959-1962 (Box 11, Folder 4000)
  - Code no.4001: American Motors Corporation and UAW Locals 72, 75, 154, 206, 412, 1961-1971 (Box 11, Folder 4001)
  - Code no.4006: Budd Company and UAW Locals 39, 92, 306, 813, 1122, 1958-1971 (Box 11, Folder 4006)
  - Code no.4012: Clark Equipment Company and UAW Local 468, 1958-1968 (Box 11, Folder 4012)
  - Code no.4013: Clark Equipment Company and Allied Industrial Workers Local 623, 1958-1971 (Box 11, Folder 4013)
  - Code no.4015: Dana Corporation and UAW Local 370, 1961-1967 (Box 11, Folder 4015)
  - Code no.4016: Parish Division, Dana Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 3733, 1960-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4016)
  - Code no.4017: Eaton Manufacturing Company, Valve Division and United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers Local 196, 1958-1967 (Box 11, Folder 4017)
  - Code no.4018: Eaton Manufacturing Company, Axle Division and Mechanics Education Society of America Local 21, 1961- 1967 (Box 12, Folder 4018)
  - Code no.4019: Ford Motor Company and UAW Local 1250, 1961-1967 (Box 12, Folder 4019)
  - Code no.4021: Fuller Manufacturing Company and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 822, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 4021)
  - Code no.4022: General Motors Corporation and UAW, 1958-1968 (Box 12, Folder 4022)
  - Code no.4023: General Motors Corporation and United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1958-1967 (Box 12, Folder 4023)
  - Code no.4024: Kelsey-Hayes Company and UAW Local 78, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 4024)
  - Code no.4025: Kelsey-Hayes Company and Allied Industrial Workers Local 670, 1958-1967 (Box 12, Folder 4025)
  - Code no.4028: Mack Trucks, Inc., Plainfield Plant and UAW Locals 343, 229, 68, 677, 1270, 1958-1970 (Box 12, Folder 4028)
  - Code no.4035: Motor Wheel Corporation and Allied Industrial Workers Local 182, 1958-1969 (Box 12, Folder 4035)
  - Code no.4036: North American Rockwell Corporation and United Automobile Corporation, 1958-1971 (Box 12, Folder 4036)
  - Code no.4038: Rockwell-Standard Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 4051, 1962-1971 (Box 13, Folder 4038)
  - Code no.4044: Twin Industries Corporation and IAM District 76, 1960-1969 (Box 13, Folder 4044)
  - Code no.4046: Kaiser Jeep Corporation and UAW Local 12, 1959-1968 (Box 13, Folder 4046)
  - Code no.4055: Boeing Company and Seattle Professional Engineering Employees Association, 1961-1965 (Box 13, Folder 4055)
  - Code no.4065: Douglas Aircraft Company and IAM Lodge 1578, 1960-1968 (Box 13, Folder 4065)
  - Code no.4067: Douglas Aircraft Company and Southern California Professional Engineering Association, 1960-1966 (Box 13, Folder 4067)
  - Code no.4068: Douglas Aircraft Company and UAW Local 1093, 1960-1965 (Box 13, Folder 4068)
  - Code no.4069: Douglas Aircraft Company and IAM Lodge 720, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 4069)
  - Code no.4077: Hayes International Corporation and UAW Local 1155, 1959-1974 (Box 13, Folder 4077)
  - Code no.4081: Lockheed-Georgia Company and Aeronautical Machinists, Lodge 709, 1960-1971 (Box 13, Folder 4081)
  - Code no.4082: Lockheed Aircraft Corporation and Engineers and Scientists Guild, 1961-1971 (Box 13, Folder 4082)
  - Code no.4089: Rohr Aircraft Association and IAM Local 964, 1960-1968 (Box 13, Folder 4089)
  - Code no.4096: United Aircraft Corporation and IAM Local 1746, 1960-1964 (Box 13, Folder 4096)
  - Code no.4106: Maryland Shipbuilding and Drydock Company and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 31, 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 4106)
  - Code no.4116: ACF Industries, Inc., American Car and Foundry Division and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1964 (Box 14, Folder 4116)
  - Code no.4119: General American Transportation Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 14, Folder 4119)
  - Code no.4120: Pullman-Standard and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1965 (Box 14, Folder 4120)
  - Code no.4137: United Aircraft Corporation and IAM Local 1746-A, 1962-1970 (Box 14, Folder 4137)
  - Code no.4405: Amtek, Inc., U.S. Gauge Division and IAM Local 1092, 1964-1967 (Box 14, Folder 4405)
  - Code no.4407: Leeds and Northrup Company and Leeds and Northrup Employees Union, 1960-1967 (Box 14, Folder 4407)
  - Code no.4411: Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Company, Robertshaw Thermostat Division and United Steelworkers of America Local 1163, 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 4411)
  - Code no.4417: E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company and International Chemical Workers Union Local 527, 1960-1968 (Box 14, Folder 4417)
  - Code no.4420: General Time Corporation, Westclox Division and UMW Local 12573, 1961-1966 (Box 14, Folder 4420)
  - Code no.4427: Xerox Corporation and Amalgamated Xerographic and Photo Supply Workers Union, 1964-1970 (Box 14, Folder 4427)
  - Code no.4600: Jewelry Manufacturers Association, Inc. and Amalgamated Jewelry, Diamond and Watchcase Workers Union Local 1, 1963- 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4600)
  - Code no.4607: Independent Doll Employers and Toy and Novelty Workers of America Local 223, 1957-1960 (Box 14, Folder 4607)
  - Code no.8301: Oliver Iron Mining Division, US Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 24, Folder 8301)
  - Code no.1114: Kirsch Company and United Automobile Association Local 797, 1961-1968 (Box 25, Folder 1114)
  - Code no.1118: Industrial Relations Council of Furniture Manufacturers in Southern California and Furniture Workers Union Local 3161, 1963-1968 (Box 25, Folder 1118)
  - Code no.2531: Lone Star Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, CIO Local 4134, 1963-1968 (Box 27, Folder 2531)
  - Code no.2592: Aluminum Company of America and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1964 (Box 27, Folder 2592)
  - Code no.2609: Revere Copper and Brass Incorporated and Mechanics Educational Society of America Local 56, 1960-1962 (Box 27, Folder 2609)
  - Code no.2618: Ladish Co. and IAM District 10, 1959-1967 (Box 27, Folder 2618)
  - Code no.2619: McLouth Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 27, Folder 2619)
  - Code no.2622: Latrobe Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 2622)
  - Code no.2625: Washington Metal Trades, Inc. and International Molders and Allied Workers Union Local 158, 1964-1967 (Box 27, Folder 2625)
  - Code no. 2627: Moore Drop Forging Company and Directly Affiliated Local Union, Local 22804, AFL-CIO (1964), 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 2627)
  - Code no.2628: Phoenix Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1962-1965 (Box 27, Folder 2628)
  - Code no.2660: National-Standard Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2660)
  - Code no.2662: Western Electric, Phoenix Plant and CWA, 1971-1974 (Box 28, Folder 2662)
  - Code no.2900: American Can Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1956-1962 (Box 28, Folder 2900)
  - Code no.2942: Mirro Aluminum Company and UMW, 1961-1969 (Box 28, Folder 2942)
  - Code no.2944: West Bend Company and Allied International Workers Local 865, 1961-1971 (Box 28, Folder 2944)
  - Code no.2950: Scovil Mfg. Co., A. Schraders' Son Division and IUE Local 458, 1958-1961 (Box 28, Folder 2950)
  - Code no.2952: Steel Fabricators and Erectors Council, Inc. and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Local 790, 1961-1971 (Box 28, Folder 2952)
  - Code no.2958: Crown Cork and Seal Company, Inc. and Can Workers' Union Local 266, 1961-1964 (Box 28, Folder 2958)
  - Code no.2962: Fisher Governor Company and UAW Local 893, 1964-1970 (Box 28, Folder 2962)
  - Code no.2977: Steel Fabricators Association of So. California, Inc. and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Local 509, 1967-1974 (Box 28, Folder 2977)
  - Code no.2978: Foster Wheeler Corporation and IAM Lodge 1665, 1968-1971 (Box 28, Folder 2978)
  - Code no.3201: Allis-Chalmers Mfg. Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 1091, 1959-1968 (Box 28, Folder 3201)
  - Code no.3204: Elliott, Division of Carrier Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1968-1974 (Box 28, Folder 3204)
  - Code no.3205: Clinton Engines Corporation and IAM AFL-CIO Local 102, 1960-1965 (Box 28, Folder 3205)
  - Code no.3211: Nordberg Manufacturing Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 1173, 1959-1966 (Box 28, Folder 3211)
  - Code no.3222: Deere and Company and UAW Locals 450, 94, 865, 1536, 81, 74, 434, 838, 1971-1973 (Box 28, Folder 3222)
  - Code no.3226: International Harvester Company and UAW, 1961-1970 (Box 28, Folder 3226)
  - Code no.3231: Cameron Iron Works, Inc. and IAM Lodge 12, 1962-1971 (Box 28, Folder 3231)
  - Code no.3233: Caterpillar Tractor Co. and IAM Lodge 851, 1959-1968 (Box 28, Folder 3233)
  - Code no.3234: Chain Belt Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 1527, 1960-1968 (Box 28, Folder 3234)
  - Code no.3242: Marion Power Shovel Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 1949, 1961-1967 (Box 28, Folder 3242)
  - Code no.3243: Eaton Yale and Towne, Inc., Yale Materials Handling Division and IAM Lodge 1717, 1959-1971 (Box 28, Folder 3243)
  - Code no.3246: Pratt and Whitney Co., Inc. and UAW Local 405, 1959-1974 (Box 28, Folder 3246)
  - Code no.3247: Ex-Cell-O Corporation and UAW Local 49, 1959-1965 (Box 28, Folder 3247)
  - Code no.3248: Gisholt Machine Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 1404, 1960-1968 (Box 28, Folder 3248)
  - Code no.3253: National Acme Company and Mechanics Educational Society of America Local 19, 1961-1967 (Box 28, Folder 3253)
  - Code no.3255: Sundstrand Corporation and UAW Local 592, 1961-1968 (Box 28, Folder 3255)
  - Code no.3258: Beloit Corporation and IAM Local 68, 1960-1971 (Box 28, Folder 3258)
  - Code no.3264: Textile Machine Works and Textile Machine Works Employees' Independent Union, 1960-1966 (Box 28, Folder 3264)
  - Code no.3265: United Shoe Machinery Corporation, Beverly Factory and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America Local 271, 1961-1973 (Box 28, Folder 3265)
  - Code no.3269: Fafnir Bearing Company and UAW Local 133, 1960-1968 (Box 28, Folder 3269)
  - Code no.3270: Federal-Mogul-Bower Bearings Inc. and UAW Local 681, 1961-1969 (Box 28, Folder 3270)
  - Code no.3274: Link-Belt Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 1150, 1959-1967 (Box 28, Folder 3274)
  - Code no.3275: Marlin-Rockwell Corporation and UAW Locals 197, 338, 1958-1967 (Box 28, Folder 3275)
  - Code no.3277: SKF Industries, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America Local 2898, 1959-1975 (Box 29, Folder 3277)
  - Code no.3279: Torrington Company and Metal Products Workers Union Local 1645, 1959-1967 (Box 29, Folder 3279)
  - Code no.3281: Addressograph-Multigraph Corporation and IAM Lodge 1228, 1960-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3281)
  - Code no.3287: Remington Rand, Inc. and IBEW Local 110, 1958-1967 (Box 29, Folder 3287)
  - Code no.3290: Underwood Corporation and IAM Lodges 19, 350, 354, 35, 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 3290)
  - Code no.3294: Copeland Refrigeration Corp. and IUE Local 725, 1961-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3294)
  - Code no.3298: Rex Manufacturing Division of Philco, Corp. and IUE Local 919, 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 3298)
  - Code no.3305: Washington Metal Trades, Inc. and IAM Local 79, 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 3305)
  - Code no.3306: Gale Products and Marine Motor Lodge No. 1659, 1962-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3306)
  - Code no.3311: Carrier Corporation and Sheet Metal Workers International Association Local 527, 1962-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3311)
  - Code no.3314: Tecumseh Products Co. and IAM Lodge 1259, 1962-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3314)
  - Code no.3318: Waukesha Motor Company and IAM Local 1377, 1963-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3318)
  - Code no.3319: J.I. Case Company and UAW CIO Locals 806, 807, 689, 858, 378, 180, 1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 3319)
  - Code no.3324: Burroughs Corporation and UAW Local 1313, 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3324)
  - Code no.3332: Massey-Ferguson Inc. and UAW Locals 174 and 256, 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3332)
  - Code no.3345: California Metal Trades Association, Printing Manufacturing and Service Division and IAM Lodge 68, 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 3345)
  - Code no.3348: Caterpillar Tractor Co. and UAW Locals 145, 215, 311, 751, 786, 790, 974, 1415, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3348)
  - Code no.3365: Mesta Machine Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1965-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3365)
  - Code no.3374: Lufkin Foundry and Machine Company and AFL-CIO, 1961-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3374)
  - Code no.3379: Contract Shops of Portland and Metal Trades Council of Portland and Vicinity, 1961-1965 (Box 29, Folder 3379)
  - Code no.3392: Norge Division, Effingham Plant and Stove Mounters' International Union of North America Local 105, 1959- 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3392)
  - Code no.3601: Federal Pacific Electric Company and IBEW Local 1159, 1956-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3601)
  - Code no.3604: Pennsylvania Transformer Division and United Steelworkers of America Local 3968, 1960-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3604)
  - Code no.3620: Reliance Electric and Engineering Co. and IUE Local 737, 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 3620)
  - Code no.3624: Wagner Electric Corporation and IUE Local 1104, 1958-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3624)
  - Code no.3626: Westinghouse Electric Corporation and IBEW Local 201, 1955-1976 (Box 29, Folder 3626)
  - Code no.3640: Singer Manufacturing Company and IUE Local 461, 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 3640)
  - Code no.3647: New York Lamp and Shade Manufacturers' Association, Inc. and IBEW Local 3, 1965-1967 (Box 29, Folder 3647)
  - Code no.3651: Collins Radio Company and IBEW Local 1362, 1961-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3651)
  - Code no.3652: Allen B. DuMont Laboratories, Inc. and IUE Local 420, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 3652)
  - Code no.3653: Emerson Television and Radio Company and IUE Local 480, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 3653)
  - Code no.3656: Electrical Transcription Labor Agreement and American Federation of Musicians, 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 3656)
  - Code no.3659: Radio Corporation of America and IUE Locals 103, 106, 177,178, 267, 439, 730, 1504, 771, 854, 971, 1203, 1967- 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3659)
  - Code no.3672: ITT Federal Laboratories and IUE Local 447, 1960-1967 (Box 30, Folder 3672)
  - Code no.3671: CBS Electronics and IUE Local 270, 1960-1962 (Box 30, Folder 3671)
  - Code no.3674: Oak Manufacturing, Inc. and IBEW Local 1031, 1959-1960 (Box 30, Folder 3674)
  - Code no.3678: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1470, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3678)
  - Code no.3680: Western Electric Company, Inc. and IBEW Local 1504, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3680)
  - Code no.3681: Western Electric Company, Inc., Montgomery Plant and IBEW Local 1942, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3681)
  - Code no.3682: Western Electric Company, Inc., Omaha Works and IBEW Local 1974, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3682)
  - Code no.3683: Western Electric Company, Inc., Oklahoma City Works and IBEW Local 2021, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3683)
  - Code no.3687: Western Electric Company, Inc., Hawthorne Works and IBEW Local 1859, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3687)
  - Code no.3688: Western Electric Company, Inc., Reading Plant and IBEW Local 1898, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3688)
  - Code no.3689: Western Electric Company, Inc., Columbus Works and IBEW Local 2020, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3689)